motivationalwellbeing.com 2016-11-28

# Legal Disclaimer | Privacy Policy - MotivationalWellBeing

  * Legal Disclaimer
  * User Submitted Content Ownership
  * Use of Content on this Site
  * Privacy Policy
  * Affiliate Disclosure

**Legal**

This web site, www.motivationalwellbeing.com, is intended to provide educational information on topics related to personal development and motivation. The publisher is not engaged in rendering legal, medical, financial, or other professional services. If expert assistance is required, please seek the services of a competent professional.

The publisher has endeavored to make the material on this site accurate. The information should be used only as general guide, however, as the publisher cannot guarantee that this information is free of typographical or content errors. Furthermore, each piece of content contains educational information only up to its original publication date.

THE INFORMATION ON THIS SITE IS PROVIDED “AS-IS”. THE AUTHOR(S) AND THE PUBLISHER WILL ASSUME NO LIABILITY NOR RESPONSIBILITY TO ANY PERSON OR ENTITY WITH RESPECT TO ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE RELATED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY TO THE INFORMATION ON THIS SITE. NO WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ARE MADE. THE PUBLISHER WILL PROVIDE NO REMEDY FOR INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES ARISING FROM THIS SITE, INCLUDING SUCH FROM NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, OR BREACH OF WARRANTY OR CONTRACT, EVEN AFTER NOTICE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. 

**Ownership of User Submitted Content**

By submitting content to this website, whether through the comments section or the contact forms, you give the owner of this website, Kevin Ngo, the rights and permission to use your content as he pleases; this includes using the content in published works for profit such as ebooks, magazines, physical books, and so on.

**Use of Content**

Aside from the quotes, poems, stories, and videos, all other content on this site is the property of Kevin Ngo (the owner of this website) and is not allowed to be copied, reproduced, or distributed in any way, shape, or form without his permission.

**Privacy Policy**

This website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when visiting this site. These third parties may collect and use information (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit [Google’s Advertising and Privacy page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you wish to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns you may do so at [Network Advertising Initiative](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Google uses the Doubleclick DART cookie to serve ads across it’s Adsense network and you can get further information regarding the DART cookie at [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) as well as opt out options at Google’s Privacy Center.

Privacy

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at motivationalwellbeing.com The following discloses how I gather and disseminate information for this site.

RSS Feeds and Email Updates

If a user wishes to subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. (You will never be spammed by me – ever)

Stats

I use Google Analytics. This stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Cookies

This site does not store cookies.

Links

This Blog contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I suggest my users to be aware of this when they leave this blog and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

Advertisers

I use outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and I do not have access to this information. The following are some of the advertising companies I use: Google Adsense, Shareasale, Amazon, and CJ.com. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.

**Affiliate Disclosure**

The products that are recommended on this site are through affiliate programs which means I get paid a commission if a visitor buys the product(s) using my link. 

I’m also a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or concerns please contact me on the contacts page. This privacy policy was updated in April 2016.
